four and three and two
[Music]
and what's up guys I'm Matt FX music
supervisor of Broad City and here is our
recap for episodes 2 and three
Weed and working girls first up we've
got a track called 1977 by Anna tiu 1977
is a very cool Latin rap Track Running
under the cold open of working girls
it's a really great identity piece in
the show kind of showing how the two
different girls go about their days
obviously Elana is a bit of a slacker
ab's a bit of an overachiever got a lot
of really great feedback on this track
so we're really happy to fature
[Music]
it secondly we're going to feature a bit
about an artist named Hot show
uh Hot Sugar is a producer who's worked
with everyone from the roots to D racist
he makes incredibly interesting unique
hip-hop beats that have an almost Wily
Wonka sort of magic to them he's
actually someone who's given us a bunch
of music for the show all of which is
unreleased so I can't even give you
track titles I can tell you that his
music is in a bunch of transitions in
episode 3 as well as some of the later
episodes in the season next up we've got
another featur transition in episode 3
in the instrumental dub of Badman by Dr
Jeep we feature badman in a transition
right before is in the train with the
cops the cops are just walking by while
she's a little uncomfortable hiding
Contraband within her person perfect
idea to use this track as it starts off
with a little siren Loop and having the
cops walking by It just fits real nicely
[Music]
together last song featured in this
recap is another episode three Jam see
you leave by the inimitable
rjd2 see you leave is running in the
dentist waiting room scene as aby's
waiting for Alana to get out of the
procedure uh it's a really early scene
in our season where we get to show aby's
funloving side and I think RJ d2's kind
of fun slow humble Groove was just a
perfect fit for her
[Music]
[Applause]
personality
right
and that was our catch-up recap for
episodes 2 and three Weed and
working girls thanks so much for
watching follow me on Twitter at Matt FX
FX FX FX four times if you have any
questions about the music on the show
follow Broad City on Facebook Tumblr or
Twitter and we'll see you next week four
and three and two
[Music]
and